[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "How many children did Steve Martins character have in the movie Planes, Trains  Automobiles?", "correct_answer": "3", "incorrect_answers": ["4", "1", "2"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What 1995 movie is this quote from: Little Tommy Daggett. How I loved listening to your sweet prayers. Then you would hop into bed, afraid that I was hiding under it. And I was!?", "correct_answer": "The Prophecy", "incorrect_answers": ["Event Horizon", "The People Under the Stairs", "Salems Lot"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the relationship between the talking beaver and the faun in the 2007 parody film Epic Movie?", "correct_answer": "They really, really like each other.", "incorrect_answers": ["None of these", "They are friends.", "They hate each other."]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Nabisco makes animal crackers in a plant located in this state.", "correct_answer": "New Jersey", "incorrect_answers": ["Utah", "Ohio", "Massachusetts"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the name of the captain of the Axiom in the film WALL-E?", "correct_answer": "Captain B. McCrea", "incorrect_answers": ["Captain  H. Nelson", "Captain E. Smith", "Captain J. Picard"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of these states has an official motto that doesnt include the word rights in it?", "correct_answer": "Indiana", "incorrect_answers": ["Iowa", "Wyoming", "Alabama"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Where was  the Transformers 2 movie filmed?", "correct_answer": "All of these", "incorrect_answers": ["California", "France", "Egypt"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In the 1950s, these electronic components replaced vacuum tubes in the production of computers.", "correct_answer": "transistors", "incorrect_answers": ["diodes", "chips", "processors"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In Ron Whites life, who is Sluggo?", "correct_answer": "his bulldog", "incorrect_answers": ["his best friend from grade school", "his shop teacher from high school", "his grandmothers neighbor"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Who portrayed Brig. Gen. Theodore Roosevelt, Jr. in The Longest Day?", "correct_answer": "Henry Fonda", "incorrect_answers": ["John Wayne", "Mel Ferrer", "Ray Danton"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Greenland is part of this country.", "correct_answer": "Denmark", "incorrect_answers": ["Iceland", "Norway", "United Kingdom"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Why does your cat interrupt you and want petting when youre on the phone?", "correct_answer": "your cat thinks you are talking to him/ her", "incorrect_answers": ["to annoy you", "to be a part of your telephone call", "your cats is jealous that youre talking to someone else"]}]